blogtopsites.com 2007-12-29

# Blog Flux Privacy Policy - Blog Flux

## Privacy Statement for Blog Flux and its associated services

**Blog Flux** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [Blog Flux](http://www.blogflux.com/)

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. For the majority of the site, the IP is simply stored for security purposes, such as a DOS attack. Your IP is not used for any other purposes. Using our [MapStats service](http://mapstats.blogflux.com/), your IP is used to obtain a location point. This IP is not shared with anyone else nor is it used for any other purpose. 

#### Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Cookies are used on Blog Flux only for login purposes. 

#### Personal Information

This Web site does not request any personal information other than your email. Your email is only used for contacting you about Blog Flux updates. Registered users on the site may also contact you through the website. If you so desire, you can cease any of these contacts through your [control panel](http://www.blogflux.com/usercp.php). Your email will also not be distributed to anyone for any purpose. If you are a subscriber to our Subscription Service, you have the option of not allowing the blog owner to see your email. 

Blog Flux maintains a strict "no-spam" policy. Your e-mail address will not be sold to a third party. At no time is personal information collected without explicit consent. 

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. **Blog Flux** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at the following page: [contact us](http://www.blogflux.com/contact.php).
